const questions = [
    {
        // Topic
        topic: "Cornwall",
        questions: [
            {
                // Question 1
                question: "What is the name of the capital city of Cornwall?",
                options: ["Penzance", "Truro", "St Ives"],
                answer: 2,      // refers to the index of the correct option
            },
            {
                // Question 2
                question: "Which of the following beaches is located near Falmouth, Cornwall?",
                options: ["Perranporth Beach", "Watergate Bay", "Gyllyngvase Beach"],
                answer: 2,
            },
            {
                // Question 3
                question: "Who was a famous pirate from Cornwall?",
                options: ["Blackbeard", "Sir Francis Drake", "John Hawkins"],
                answer: 1,
            },
            {
                // Question 4
                question: "What is the name of the largest prehistoric monument in Cornwall?",
                options: ["The Hurlers", "The Merry Maidens", "Stonehenge"],
                answer: 0,
            },
            {
                // Question 5
                question: "Which of the following Cornwall towns is known for its Eden Project?",
                options: ["St Austell", "Truro", "Newquay"],
                answer: 0,
            },
            {
                // Question 6
                question: "Who was a famous artist from Newlyn, Cornwall?",
                options: ["Jogn Singer Sargent", "Walter Sickert", "Laura Knight"],
                answer: 2,
            },
            {
                // Question 7
                question: "What is the name of the highest point in Cornwall?",
                options: ["Brown Willy", "Carn Menellis", "The Hurlers"],
                answer: 0,
            },
            {
                // Question 8
                question: "Which of the following harbours is located near St Ives, Cornwall?",
                options: ["Falmouth Harbour", "Mousehole Harbour", "St Ives Harbour"],
                answer: 2,
            },
            {
                // Question 9
                question: "Who was a famous author from Cornwall?",
                options: ["Daphne du Maurier", "Rosamunde Pilcher", "Helen Dunmore"],
                answer: 0,
            },
            {
                // Question 10
                question: "What is the name of the River that flows through Truro, Cornwall?",
                options: ["Fowey River", "Tamar River", "Kenwyn River"],
                answer: 0
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        // Topic
        topic: "Pop-music trivia",
        questions: [
            {}
        ]
    }
]